So Claude can now read my Twitter feed.
Now I don't like scrolling through X,
there are some weird people on X.
But there's actually a ridiculous amount
of very useful information
that sometimes gets posted.
So I found an open source Python framework
called Browser Use.
It allows AI to control your web browser
kind of like a human would.
And for the local browser version,
you don't actually need an X API
or the Browser Use cloud API.
So what I told it to do was go
through my X home feed, scroll
through roughly like a hundred posts,
ignore the memes, engagement bait,
and repeated stories, then find 10 things
most relevant to AI agents, developer
tools, startups, and new products.
For each, tell me what happened,
why it matters, and give me
the original post.